A Guide to the Papers of Anne Spencer and the Spencer Family, 1829, 1864-2007
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Manuscripts and Poems (Box-folder 17:7-22:55)
  - Poems and Other (Box-folder 21:20-22:55)
    - n.d. Poem "White Things" (Box-folder 22:50))
    - n.d. Poem "The Wife-Woman" (Box-folder 22:51))
    - 1976 Poems by Anne Spencer - Typescript Copies by Lee Greene (Box-folder 22:52))
    - n.d. Poetry Fragments (Box-folder 22:53))
    - [post 1943-48], n.d. Quotations by [?] Field, Oliver Wendell Holmes, [Xenophon?], and others (Box-folder 22:54))
    - n.d. Short Story "A True Story of our Joe, A Crow" believed to be by Anne Spencer (Box-folder 22:55))